T.B. Joshua opens a school donated by Emmanuel TV in Ecuador 2017.
After a 7,8 magnitude earthquake struck northern Ecuador in April 2016,
T.B. Joshua and partners of Emmanuel TV reached out with humanitarian aid and rebuilt the school,
providing help in an indigenous community.
Prophet T.B. Joshua welcomed by generals of the Ecuador Military
arrives in Ecuador for the opening of the new school donated by Emmanuel TV.
T.B. Joshua Is Welcomed By Military Generals As He Arrives In Ecuador To Open The New School Donated By Emmanuel TV
Welcome Prophet T.B. Joshua to Ecuador.
I am Sebastian.
Thank you and amen!
Thank you.
As children honour the Prophet with flowers, the representatives of the Ecuador Military
escort the Prophet through the international airport of Quito
T.B. Joshua Is Welcomed By Military Generals As He Arrives In Ecuador To Open The New School Donated By Emmanuel TV
Prophet T.B. Joshua, I am Lieutenant Omar Cruz.
It is a pleasure and joy to have you in our country, Ecuador.
I can feel the power of God around you.
The Holy Spirit is surrounding you.
We also welcome your wife to Ecuador.
Thank you.
Prophet, blessings to you.
Greeting from the Christian Police of Ecuador.
It is truly an honour to have you here
and we know that you bring great blessings from our Heavenly Father.
We also welcome your wife.
The doors of Ecuador are open for you.
God bless you.
Among the welcoming committee is General Carlos Medina,
overseeing human resources in the Ecuador army.
Among other military and police authorities, the military generals escort him to the awaiting vehicle,
where all are happy and grateful for the Prophet's visit to their nation.
T.B. Joshua Is Welcomed By Military Generals As He Arrives In Ecuador To Open The New School Donated By Emmanuel TV
T.B. Joshua opens a school in Ecuador.
Generals of the Ecuadorian military welcome T.B. Joshua.
T.B. Joshua Is Conveyed With A Police Escort For A Meeting With Ecuadorian Military Generals
General Carlos Medina Of The Ecuadorian Army Welcomes T.B. Joshua To The Military Meeting
T.B. Joshua Arrives For A Meeting With Ecuadorian Military Generals
Security Forces At The Meeting Between T.B. Joshua And The Ecuadorian Military Generals
General Carlos Medina Of The Ecuadorian Army Meets With T.B. Joshua
General Carlos Medina Presents T.B. Joshua With a Symbolic Gift From The Ecuadorian Military
T.B. JOSHUA OPENS SCHOOL IN ECUADOR 2017
Meeting Ecuador's Vice President
T.B. Joshua Accompanied By Rabbi Yehuda Leaves His Hotel In Quito, Ecuador
As T.B. Joshua departs his hotel, he is met by Mrs Cinthia Glas, the wife of the vice-president of Ecuador,
who came to escort him to the presidential palace to meet her husband.
This is the Government Palace of Quito, Ecuador,
the residence of the President of the Republic of Ecuador,
and the work place of the President and Vice-President.
Carondelet, Government Palace, Quito, Ecuador
Here is the President of Ecuador waving his hands to the crowd,
and standing next to him is the Vice-President of Ecuador.
Carondelet, Government Palace, Quito, Ecuador
Ecuador Charity 2017
Inside Carondelet - The Government Palace, Quito, Ecuador
Members of the Ecuadorian Honour Guard are on duty at the palace
in full ceremonial uniform for the official meeting.
Inside Carondelet - The Government Palace, Quito, Ecuador
The sign declares that entry is exclusively for the President, Vice-President
and ministers of the State of Ecuador.
Ecuador Charity 2017
T.B. Joshua & Rabbi Yehuda At Carondelet – The Government Palace, Quito, Ecuador
T.B. Joshua is led through the Presidential Palace to the office of the Vice-President.
This is Jorge Glas, the Vice-President of the Republic of Ecuador.
Vice-President Of Ecuador, Jorge Glas Welcomes T.B. Joshua To The Government Palace
T.B. Joshua Meets With Vice-President Jorge Glas At The Governmental Palace, Quito, Ecuador
T.B. Joshua & Rabbi Yehuda With Jorge Glas Vice-President Of Ecuador
T.B. Joshua & Mrs Evelyn Joshua With Jorge Glas Vice-President of Ecuador & His Wife
T.B. Joshua Leaving The Government Palace, Quito, Ecuador
T.B. JOSHUA OPENS SCHOOL IN ECUADOR 2017
THE JOURNEY TO THE SCHOOL
T.B. Joshua & Team Arrive At The Tropical Rainforest To Continue Their Journey To The School
Now, the journey to the new school begins.
Located in a remote area, 3 hours inside the Mache Chindul Ecological Reserve, transportation is difficult.
Five hours from Quito, inside the province of Esmeraldas,
the school can be reached only by 4x4 off-road vehicles or canoes,
but when conditions are bad, only on foot.
T.B. Joshua & Team Arrive At The Tropical Rainforest To Continue Their Journey To The School
T.B. Joshua and the Emmanuel TV team start their journey in 4x4 vehicles, into the jungle of Ecuador.
Not wanting his team to pass through the difficult elements, he has them enter inside the vehicle,
while he climbs into the back.
T.B. Joshua & Team Travel In 4x4 Vehicles Through A Tropical Rainforest To Reach The School
As they get deeper and deeper into the heart of the jungle, tropical rain suddenly starts to fall,
and the journey which had been smooth so far was about to take a more challenging turn.
T.B. Joshua & Team Travel In 4x4 Vehicles Through A Tropical Rainforest To Reach The School
The rain get heavier and heavier until the vehicle gets stuck in the mud of the mountain roads.
Due To Heavy Rainfall The Vehicle Carrying T.B. Joshua & Team Gets Stuck In The Mud
With the important opening of the school just hours away,
T.B. Joshua and the Emmanuel TV team have no choice but to continue on foot.
Due To Heavy Rainfall The Vehicle Carrying T.B. Joshua & Team Gets Stuck In The Mud
T.B. Joshua & Team Continue Their Journey To The School On Foot
T.B. Joshua & Team Enter A Second 4x4 Vehicle To Continue Their Journey To The School
However, with the wet and sticky conditions not easing off,
the vehicle soon gets stuck again, in another deep rut.
The Second Vehicle Also Gets Stuck In The Mud Due To Heavy Rainfall
T.B. Joshua encourages the team with a smile,
as they have to walk through the jungle in the pouring rain, yet again.
The local guides show T.B. Joshua an ingenious way of using the big leafy branches of plants
to shield themselves from the worst of the rain.
With a genuine smile, he obligingly tries it out, holding the giant leaf over his head,
as they continue the arduous track through the mountain pass.
T.B. Joshua Is Given A Giant Leaf From The Rainforest To Use As An Umbrella
T.B. Joshua & Team Walk Through The Tropical Rainforest In Heavy Rain To Reach The School
They reached the descent, and the road leads steeply downhill, as they draw nearer to their destination.
T.B. Joshua & Team Finally Sight The School Donated By Emmanuel TV
An encouraging sight - the community finally comes into view,
as they take a turn on one of the ridges, and motivated the team begins to pick up their pace,
now that the end is in sight.
Peering through the vegetation, you can see the school
built and donated by T.B. Joshua and Emmanuel TV partners,
nestling into the midst of the community, on the site of the previous school,
which was destroyed during the horrendous earthquake of April 2016.
This is the Juan Lorenzo Anapa School.
U.E.C.I.B Juan Lorenzo Anapa School Donated By Emmanuel TV For Nursery, Primary & Secondary Education
T.B. Joshua & Team Finally Sight The School Donated By Emmanuel TV
T.B. Joshua & Team Walk Down The Mountain In Heavy Rain To Reach The School
T.B. Joshua & Team Arrive At The Community Where The School Is Located
They have reached the community and stoically forge on till they arrive at the school itself,
to commence its historic opening day.
Parents & Students Welcome T.B. Joshua & Team To The School Donated By Emmanuel TV
Ecuadorian Students Welcome T.B. Joshua & Team To The School Donated By Emmanuel TV
T.B. JOSHUA OPENS SCHOOL IN ECUADOR 2017
The opening of the school
The Teachers & Students Perform Traditional Dances To Welcome T.B. Joshua
The Emmanuel TV Team Joins The Teachers & Students In The Dance
Students Welcome T.B. Joshua To The New School For The Opening Day Ceremony
T.B. Joshua Arrives At The Opening Ceremony For The New School Donated By Emmanuel TV
Thank you, children; thank you very much.
I want to thank you in the name of Jesus and I am here today by instruction.
Going by what I have gone through before coming here,
it is not just possible for anyone without God’s instruction to be here.
But I am here on God’s command.
Opening Ceremony – Juan Lorenzo Anapa School Donated by Emmanuel TV in Ecuador
What I went through today reminds me of the beginning of my ministry.
If you watch my documentary, you will see the similarity of what I went through today.
Opening Ceremony – Juan Lorenzo Anapa School Donated by Emmanuel TV in Ecuador
For our children and our young people, it is a pleasure to support.
Even in a rare situation, we are ready because you are the leaders of tomorrow.
Opening Ceremony – Juan Lorenzo Anapa School Donated by Emmanuel TV in Ecuador
What you are seeing around in terms of buildings or whatever -
we are not doing it for you; we are doing it for ourselves,
knowing that serving God is helping our children, neighbours and fellow brothers.
Thank you very much.
My name is T.B. Joshua, your brother, your servant. Just take me, accept me.
Opening Ceremony – Juan Lorenzo Anapa School Donated by Emmanuel TV in Ecuador
Hallelujah!
This occasion would not have taken place without our community here -
our teachers, neighbours and children.
The leadership in the school and the leadership in the community – thank you very much
for making this occasion possible.
Opening Ceremony – Juan Lorenzo Anapa School Donated by Emmanuel TV in Ecuador
We are here in the name of Jesus Christ
who gave us strength and ability to do whatever we are doing.
With respect and honour, I want to thank you for coming
to the ribbon cutting opening ceremony of this school.
We are going to cut this in the name of the Father, the Son and the Holy Spirit.
Thank you.
Bless you, Father, Son and Holy Spirit.
T.B. Joshua Cuts The Ribbon To Open The School Donated By Emmanuel TV
T.B. Joshua Unveils The Commemorative Plaque At The Lorenzo Anapa School in Ecuador
Ecuador Charity 2017
Thank you.
Yes, going by the reading here,
for our children,
our young people,
it is a pleasure to help and to support them.
We are ready to do every proper thing -
our best time, our quality time, what we cherish most, what our life depends on,
to support them because they are the leaders of tomorrow.
Here is the future of Ecuador.
The kings, the queens, the president, the royals and the high profile personalities are sitting here.
I want to salute you - thank you for giving me the privilege to contribute a little into your life.
Thank you very much.
Distinguished T.B. Joshua, welcome to our community.
In this historic moment, on behalf of the community, we want to present you with
all that is produced in this area.
The Community Members Present T.B. Joshua With Locally Farmed Produce & Items
Locally Farmed Produce & Items
Local produce is presented to T.B. Joshua as a gift from the community.
Among the textile producst of the region, he is given this traditional bright blue shirt,
which T.B. Joshua gladly accepts and starts to wear.
T.B. Joshua Wears The Shirt Made By The Community Members & Samples The Local Fruit
He wholeheartedly samples some of the locally farmed crops and fruits native to Ecuador,
in appreciation of their gift.
T.B. Joshua Wears The Shirt Made By The Community Members & Samples The Local Fruit
I'm a farmer.
We come together to see what we can do to support the farmers here.
T.B. Joshua In The Community Of San Salvador De Los Chachis
So, thank you very much.
T.B. Joshua At The Opening Day Of School Built And Donated By Emmanuel TV In Ecuador
After the ribbon cutting opening ceremony, and officially declaring the school open,
T.B. Joshua spends time moving around to greet members of the community.
Here, T.B. Joshua meets the medical professionals, posted by the government to serve the community.
T.B. Joshua At The Opening Day Of School Built And Donated By Emmanuel TV In Ecuador
Our strength comes from God.
Jesus gave us enablement to do what we are doing.
He has no hands but our hands.
He has no tongue but our tongue.
So, we are here today to cut this cake at the count of Jesus.
T.B. Joshua With Students Of The Juan Lorenzo Anapa School Donated By Emmanuel TV
Thank you.
In the name of Jesus Christ, we pray for the community.
We pray for the children here today.
We pray for your parents, our staff and our teachers and guardians.
We pray for the leadership in Ecuador for the protection of God.
In Jesus Christ's name.
Amen.
Thank you.
T.B. Joshua With Children Of The Juan Lorenzo Anapa School Donated By Emmanuel TV
God bless you all.
It is an honour for me to first give thanks to God for the presence of Prophet T.B. Joshua
and everyone here.
With all my heart, the students of The Juan Lorenzo Anapa School appreciate you
for giving us classrooms of such quality that we didn’t have before.
Now we have this new school, we can study better and more comfortably.
We thank God for what happened on April 16 so that we could have something better.
Because after what happened on April 16, God touched the heart of
this organisation, Emmanuel TV and that is why we have this school.
Although you come from a far country, you have always been close to this community and the country, Ecuador.
That is why the students are very grateful for all that you have done.
I am from a different community but thanks to this school, I have the opportunity to study well.
I want to appreciate all the effort and love that the organisation, Emmanuel TV
has shown towards this community.
Thank you for everything and for giving us a new school.
Thank you, Prophet T.B. Joshua.
We love you!
T.B. JOSHUA OPENS SCHOOL IN ECUADOR 2017
The opening of the school.
U.E.C.I.B Juan Lorenzo Anapa School Donated By Emmanuel TV For Nursery, Primary & Secondary Education
These are the class rooms and amenities built and financed solely
by Emmanuel TV partners across the world, and T.B. Joshua.
The school consists of several classroom blocks, for the different years of students in attendance,
and can comfortably accommodate over 300 people.
Taking a look inside of one of the classrooms, we can see that it is large and spacious enough
to hold classes of over 30 people.
The brand new, specially designed chairs have a sturdy wooden desk and shelf
to enable the children to study and keep their bags and items neatly.
Inside The Classrooms Built And Furnished With Desks And Chairs By Emmanuel TV
The sign on a door reminds students to live their life by serving others,
as they are welcomed into the classroom.
The Students Enter Their New Classrooms
The excited Ecuadorian children are taken to their new classrooms and happily take their seats.
Each of the different classes, according to their age ranges and level
are guided into the right place and happily scurry to take their position at their new desks.
The Students Enter Their New Classrooms
The Students Seated In Their New Classrooms
As T.B. Joshua begins to move around the premises, this little boy seizes the opportunity to give him a hug,
thanking him for his new school.
T.B. Joshua & Team Walk Around The Premises Of The School Donated By Emmanuel TV
T.B. Joshua Enters The Classrooms Of The School Donated By Emmanuel TV
He is taken around each of the classrooms and reaffirming his earlier statement,
greets and gives a handshake to each of the children - the future of Ecuador.
T.B. Joshua Greets The Students
Before leaving this room, T.B. Joshua writes a message on the board for the children to keep in their hearts
that Jesus loves them.
And he has it written in Spanish too.
T.B. Joshua Greets The Students
T.B. Joshua Greets The Teacher & Students
Moving on to the next class, where he continues giving a word of encouragement,
and personally welcomes each pupil to their new class.
He thanks the teacher and the students give a round of applause in appreciation.
Then, the man of God is taken to the section for the youngest classes of students.
T.B. Joshua Greets The Teacher and Students
T.B. Joshua Greets The Students
While interacting with this girl, he writes the message he wants each of them to have no doubt of,
that Jesus loves them.
T.B. Joshua & Team Walk Around The Premises Of The School Donated By Emmanuel TV
T.B. Joshua Greets The Teacher & Students
T.B. Joshua Greets The Students
Still on the go, the man of God had to climb the long walkway to the top level of the school,
to meet the senior students.
T.B. Joshua Greets The Students
T.B. Joshua Enters The School Classrooms To Greet The Students
T.B. Joshua Greets The Teacher & Students
T.B. Joshua Greets The Students
T.B. Joshua joyfully moves on to the next class to extend the hand of God's love and friendship to them,
as they start a new school career.
T.B. Joshua Greets The Students
T.B. Joshua & Team Walk Around The Premises Of The School Donated By Emmanuel TV
As T.B. Joshua finished moving around each of the classrooms,
a delicious meal and fruit drink was shared to each of the students and staff,
to celebrate the historic opening of the school.
Celebratory Meal Shared With The New School’s Students
As the meals were being taken around, T.B. Joshua also called on the Emmanuel TV team
to join him giving out Emmanuel TV gift bags.
School Gift Bags Shared With Students Of The New School
To complete his tour of the premises, T.B. Joshua is shown the new toilet facilities,
and he inspects them with the nod of satisfaction.
T.B. Joshua Is Shown The Toilet Facilities Of The New School Donated By Emmanuel TV
Clean Running Water From A Borehole Supplied & Blessed By Prophet T.B. Joshua
In the name of Jesus - thank you.
As you can see, now we are seeing a water tank.
This water is coming from the rain.
It is collected when it rains and this is the water they used to use
before Prophet T.B. Joshua sponsored and built this wonderful school
and provided this water supply from a borehole.
This borehole is solely to supply water for this school.
Emmanuel TV disaster relief; on this site stands the newly constructed
Unidad Educativa Juan Lorenzo Anapa, built and donated by philanthropist T.B. Joshua,
founder of Emmanuel TV, following the earthquake of April 2016.
Official opening: May 18, 2017.
"You don't give; you don't receive. Start giving!" T.B. Joshua.
Ecuador Charity 2017
The ceremonial plaque was written in both English and Spanish for the benefit of the people of Ecuador.
T.B. JOSHUA OPENS SCHOOL IN ECUADOR 2017
Community comments.
Antonin Tapuyo
Auxiliary Nurse
I have been working with the Ministry Of Public Health for 36 years.
The government brought me here to work together with my people.
I thank Prophet T.B. Joshua for this great work that has made history in the Chachi community.
For this reason, we are very grateful for that school that we never expected to have
and for this great contribution from the prophet to the people who need it most in Ecuador.
As a nursing professional, I am very grateful to this organisation, Emmanuel TV.
Pastor Margarita Alcibar
Foundation Ministry Reaching The Nations
We are very grateful to the Lord and to Prophet T.B. Joshua for coming to Ecuador.
Many institutions do not look at remote places in mountains and rural areas
but we give thanks to the Lord because Prophet T.B. Joshua has made a difference.
He has taught us what the Bible says that it is better to give than to receive.
We are very grateful because he has come with his whole team to Ecuador
who worked really hard in this community.
God bless you.
Jimmy Vera
Medical Doctor
I have been sent by the government to help this community.
I am very grateful to Prophet T.B. Joshua and to his international Christian organisation
for having considered this indigenous community that is in need.
I am very grateful to him and his team for bringing joy to this community
and for building these classrooms which are of vital importance to the children.
Emmanuel TV, I am very grateful to you. Thank you.
Luis Cantos
Dentist
I am in my practical year and the government sent me to this rural community.
I am very happy with what Emmanuel TV has done for the people.
They have given the children a brand new modern school
and I am happy that they can now excel in their studies.
Doctor Yamil
Community Medical Doctor
The foundation, Emmanuel TV has done a great work in this community.
We are talking about a school, an institution that all communities need.
I believe it is an international aid and solidarity that has come to support us in Ecuador.
The work that the government is supposed to do in the communities – you are doing it.
On behalf of the students of this community who are beneficiaries of this school,
I want to appreciate you from my heart and may your life be always full of blessings.
Doctor Yamil
Community Medical Doctor
Keep watching Emmanuel TV.
T.B. JOSHUA OPENS SCHOOL IN ECUADOR 2017
The journey back.
As T.B. Joshua's vehicle departed the school, due to the heavy rain which had fallen,
the vehicle loses its track and begins to slip and slide in the thick mud.
Driving Through The Tropical Rainforest T.B. Joshua's Vehicle Gets Stuck In The Mud
Even when the team gets out and pushes the vehicle, after just a short distance,
the car slides back down even further.
Driving Through The Tropical Rainforest T.B. Joshua's Vehicle Gets Stuck In The Mud
T.B. Joshua & The Emmanuel TV Team Have No Option But To Continue Their Journey On Foot
It is a long, tiring, almost two-hour walk back to the city, made all the more difficult by the thick squelchy mud.
A local farmer happens to pass by at that exact moment.
As he sees the team wading through the mud, he offers to take two people with him on the horse.
Ever the man of compassion, T.B. Joshua announces Mrs Evelyn Joshua and one of the team
to take the horse ride, while they continue on foot, along the muddy path.
OK, the two of you – tell him.
For two of you?
Yes.
Two can go with him.
A Local Farmer Passing By Offers To Help By Carrying Two People On His Horse
Two Of The Team Continue The Journey Back From The School On Horseback
T.B. Joshua & The Rest Of The Team Continue The Journey On Foot
Viewers, see me eating like any other person on the street.
Yes, I am running out of food.
That is humanitarian work for you.
Many a time we do this humanitarian work for God’s sake
and we run out of what we have given.
We went to give blessing; now, we are running out of that blessing.
Occasionally, this has to happen to test our faith, to test our genuineness, to test our gracious giving -
whether it is genuine or not.
It is not all the time you give and God supplies.
At times, you give and the supply will not come.
Our vehicle cannot go any further.
They are looking for another vehicle.
Sometimes, you may not find a vehicle – we will sleep here.
Are you not ready to sleep?
We are ready to sleep!
Yes, sir!
We are going on a mission and it is not all missions that are smooth.
Some can be very, very tough.
We are just experiencing this now – the toughest mission we are experiencing, we are going through
and it is a blessing.
What a rare privilege to suffer for the needy.
There are many people out there but God chose us to come and do this.
I can see a snail!
While Walking Back From The School T.B. Joshua Sights A Snail
Come and see the snail.
Yes, it is a big snail.
Not snake; it’s a snail.
Don’t let viewers feel threatened.
We are not looking for snakes; this is a snail.
Do you want to take this snail?
While Walking Back From The School T.B. Joshua Sights A Snail
Wonderful – but we don’t know where to eat it.
We need a fire.
Let’s ask this man if he can help us; we have to eat.
How are you?
Ask him whether he has seen the horse.
Did you see someone on a horse now?
From here? No.
No, he hasn't.
We are waiting for a horse which was carrying our loved ones.
When we were coming, the vehicle could not go – we were too many.
A man with a horse helped to carry two of us; we are waiting for them.
Where is he living?
Here.
OK, this house?
I hope you will host us today if we cannot go?
Of course, no problem!
T.B Joshua & His Team Encounter A Local Farmer Living Close By Who Agrees To Host Them
He says it is not far, he used to walk here every day.
The young man, also a local farmer, offers T.B. Joshua and the team a place to take a breather,
while they wait for the team on the horse.
T.B Joshua & His Team Encounter A Local Farmer Living Close By Who Agrees To Host Them
You can see the gate of my brother; we are just entering the gate.
This is the house we are going to.
T.B Joshua & His Team Encounter A Local Farmer Living Close By Who Agrees To Host Them
Occasionally, times can come this way.
Whatever comes, we have to accept it.
We went to give food; we are running out of food now.
We went to give help; we are running out of help now.
Sometimes, our faith can be tested.
It is not every time you give help that you will be helped.
So, this is the man God sent to us this time.
T.B. Joshua is introduced to the man's family and greets his daughter.
Thank you very much.
He wanted to go to the school but it was raining and he couldn't make it there.
I want to give them this 100 USD.
Thank you.
T.B. Joshua blesses the family with 100 USD, before he and the team take their leave.
T.B. Joshua & His Team Head Back To The Muddy Trail To Continue Their Journey
They make their way down the hill again, back to the road through the jungle.
Waving joyfully even after the long day, Mrs Joshua arrives on a horse and the team gets ready
to re-enter the vehicles and continue on their journey back to the city.
Before leaving, T.B. Joshua thanks the farmer who had assisted them with his horse.
T.B. Joshua Thanks The Local Farmer Who Provided The Horse
OK, let's go.
T.B. Joshua & His Team Enter The Vehicle To Continue Their Journey Back
He asks for help in removing his muddy boots, as the team gets ready to depart.
T.B. JOSHUA OPENS SCHOOL IN ECUADOR 2017
The journey back.
With the community members waving a fond farewell, the Emmanuel TV team pack up their equipment,
and set about preparing for their journey back to the city.
While T.B. Joshua took the path of the mountain roads, due to the muddy conditions,
the rest of the team were going to travel by river in wooden canoes.
They are off, down the river.
Emmanuel TV Team Travels By Canoe Through The Tropical Rainforest
Where traditional punting failed, the guides had to get out and physically push the boats
along the river's shallow course.
Back to deeper waters, the canoes can start speeding along nicely.
Emmanuel TV Team Travels By Canoe Through The Tropical Rainforest
Even with the unrelenting rain, the level of the river is too low for the canoes
to use their on-board motors in many places.
Emmanuel TV Team Travels By Canoe Through The Tropical Rainforest
As the skilled guides continue to navigate the long journey,
you really get the feel of how much a part of their everyday life
the river is to this community, deep in the jungle.
Emmanuel TV Team Travels By Canoe Through The Tropical Rainforest
At a point, the team has gone as far as they can by river and disembark from the boats.
Next, the Emmanuel TV team climbs aboard a couple of pick up trucks,
on the other side of the river bank to continue on to the city.
Emmanuel TV Team Boards Pick Up Trucks To Continue Their Journey Back
Emmanuel TV Team On The Last Stage Of Their Journey Back
T.B. JOSHUA OPENS SCHOOL IN ECUADOR 2017
The appreciation ceremony.
The distinguished guests begin to arrive with their families for the meeting.
Each of the dignitaries are welcomed warmly by the Emmanuel TV team as they arrive.
Let us hear a few words from some of the special guests who came to grace the event.
Engineer Efren Reyes
Deputy Minister Of Social & Economic Inclusion of Ecuador
Good evening. My name is Efren Reyes.
I am from Quito, Ecuador and I am Deputy Minister of Social and Economic Inclusion.
It is a pleasure for me to be here with Emmanuel TV.
We thank Emmanuel TV for the invitation to be a part of this event which is very important for us
because I believe it is the climax of Emmanuel TV’s humanitarian aid in Ecuador.
Within that was all the relief aid and foodstuffs that were donated to the earthquake victims.
I joined Emmanuel TV to distribute the relief aid to the shelters, especially in Esmeraldas.
We found an area in need of help, the indigenous Chachi community which needed a school.
Made aware of the need, Emmanuel TV helped by building a school for the children.
We are very happy that now the school is completed and ready
for the children of the Chachi community to begin their studies.
It is a pleasure to talk about the reason that we are here.
We are here because Emmanuel TV has done a lot of things for Ecuador,
after an earthquake that we suffered last year.
They helped us with 20 tons of aid relief, that we shared in shelters in Esmeraldas province,
in coordination with us, the Ministry of Social Inclusion; we helped many families affected by the earthquake.
Also, Emmanuel TV identified a community that was in need of a school,
and they decided to do a project to give the opportunity of education
to the children from the Chachi community.
It is a pleasure for us to be here.
The Emmanuel TV team is committed to helping those in need.
This is the reason we have formed this great working team, stronger together.
I really think that Emmanuel TV Team and T.B. Joshua are great people.
I can say that we have created a team.
We have worked together and I have seen that they have these warm feelings for the people,
this sense of helping others.
That's why I'm saying that together we are stronger.
Engineer Efren Reyes
Deputy Minister Of Social & Economic Inclusion of Ecuador
Keep watching Emmanuel TV!
More and more of the special guests representing the Ecuadorian government and military
continue to arrive for the event, and are entertained with some delicacies before the event begins.
Dignitaries Arrive For The Appreciation Ceremony
Let us listen to General Director of Human Resources of the Ecuadorian Army,
and other ranking officers, as they arrive at the event.
Brigadier-General Carlos Medina
General Director Of Human Resources, Ecuador Army
It is an honour to welcome Prophet T.B. Joshua to this country
and because of him, our citizens have been beneficiaries of humanitarian aid
and now, a school has been built to benefit the community affected by the earthquake.
We are forever grateful to Prophet T.B. Joshua and the Emmanuel TV Team.
We hope that you will enjoy the beauty of Ecuador.
We welcome you to this country with open arms.
Sergeant Joffre Echeverria
Works In Artillery Army Command Office
First Sergeant Patricio Martinez
Human Resources, Ecuadorian Army
Corporal Lituma Roberto Fernando
Colonel Santiago Armas
Logistics Commander
Lieutenant Colonel Omar Cruz
Head Of Inventory, Ecuadorian Army
We are grateful for all the support that Emmanuel TV has given our community.
God bless you.
Captain Morocho Marcos
Captain Of Transport Under General Medina
Lieutenant Gerardo Ramos
Deputy Director Of Protocol Of Social Communication Of The Ecuadorian Army
I really appreciate all the work done by Emmanuel TV.
Thank you so much on behalf of the whole country.
Police Major Byron Liger
Deputy Director, The National Immigration Police & Part Of The Global Christian Police Network
A big hug for Prophet T.B. Joshua and the ministry of Emmanuel TV.
The last of the dignitaries arrive and take a few moments to relax with some light refreshments
in the company of the other guests, as the event is about ready to begin.
Let us listen to Colonel Eddy Sanchez, the representative of the mayor of Quito.
Colonel Eddy Sanchez
Councillor Of Quito City Government
I am Colonel Eddy Sanchez.
I am from Quito, I am a Christ's soldier and a Council member.
This is the gratitude of a nation who are here today to thank Prophet T.B. Joshua
for these 20 tonnes of relief aid, medicine, love and healing that arrived after April, 2016
when the earthquake struck the Ecuadorian coast with suffering.
This message of love and seed of care arrived which is reflected in the building of the school
and hundreds of families that were beneficiaries of these 20 tonnes of aid.
We are very happy for this.
We appreciate and celebrate what Prophet T.B. Joshua and Emmanuel TV have done for Ecuador.
We are here to appreciate those 20 tonnes of aid relief that he sent.
They were 20 tonnes of love, of help, of charity for our people after the earthquake on April 2016.
We are here to appreciate him, because he also decided to help the community's children
by building a new school.
Colonel Eddy Sanchez
Councillor Of Quito City Government
Keep watching Emmanuel TV!
God bless you all.
It is time for the appreciation ceremony to begin
and the dignitaries and distinguished guests enter the hall to take their seats.
Dignitaries & Guests Enter The Hall For The Appreciation Ceremony
Ecuador Charity 2017
This is the reason of today's event;
the donation and rebuilding of the school by Emmanuel TV and T.B. Joshua.
Ecuador Charity 2017
A banner shows how the former facility was destroyed in the 2016 earthquake, the reconstruction process,
and finally, the new school donated by the Emmanuel TV partners and T.B. Joshua.
Let the ceremony begin.
T.B. JOSHUA OPENS SCHOOL IN ECUADOR 2017
The appreciation ceremony.
As the Bible says, it is more blessed to give than to receive.
The Emmanuel TV Team is very blessed today and appreciative for your presence.
Government Appreciation Ceremony In Quito For Ecuador School Donated By Emmanuel TV
Any moment from now, T.B. Joshua will join us.
And he will speak to us.
Government Appreciation Ceremony In Quito For Ecuador School Donated By Emmanuel TV
He has made the journey with a team all the way from Nigeria specifically for this occasion.
This school project is more than just a school you can see on the outside.
Government Appreciation Ceremony In Quito For Ecuador School Donated By Emmanuel TV
It’s an expression of love from the heart.
The Bible encourages us that love is always looking out to see those who are in need.
Ecuador Charity 2017
And following that terrible earthquake, the Chache community was in a desperate need.
Government Appreciation Ceremony In Quito For Ecuador School Donated By Emmanuel TV
Right now, I’d like us all to welcome T.B. Joshua who is going to come and speak to us.
Thank you, you may be seated, thank you.
Where will I start from?
Let’s allow God to direct us.
With due respect and honour, I would like to recognise some of the dignitaries here before I introduce myself.
I want to thank you for coming here – a very big thanks.
Thank you very much.
Now, I can introduce myself.
I am your brother; my name is T.B. Joshua.
I am truly humbled and honoured to be here today with my wife, children and some of my team
and with a high profile humanitarian personality here in our midst with us, the founder of ZAKA.
Just as we are Emmanuel TV, he is the founder of ZAKA – Israeli Search And Rescue Organisation.
Thank you very much.
I don’t want to forget how I heard about the trouble in Ecuador.
I was watching a channel that night and I saw that earthquake
and I saw children’s schools collapse.
I said, “Wow!”; I was touched.
Government Appreciation Ceremony In Quito For Ecuador School Donated By Emmanuel TV
I quickly sent a message to all my teams all over the world that they should watch the news,
that something had happened in Ecuador, that I was touched and that we had to come to rescue.
This is how our journey began.
This occasion would not have taken place here without the people of Ecuador,
the leaders in the school
and also the leaders in the community of the children’s school.
I want to say a very big thanks for their support.
Government Appreciation Ceremony In Quito For Ecuador School Donated By Emmanuel TV
Knowing God, serving God is helping people.
When we say we know God, we must help people; we must support people.
We must make sure whatever we can do to rescue people, we must do it.
That is serving God.
For our people, for our children in Ecuador and all over the world,
it is a pleasure to do every proper thing to support them.
We are ready to give our life to make sure they remain the leaders of tomorrow.
This is why we are here.
Government Appreciation Ceremony In Quito For Ecuador School Donated By Emmanuel TV
One thing we need to know about our team -
they are always ready to change lives, change nations and change the world.
You are welcome to join us.
Government Appreciation Ceremony In Quito For Ecuador School Donated By Emmanuel TV
Thank you very much.
We would like to acknowledge the presence of some particular people here, locally from Ecuador.
We are very privileged to have everyone of you with us, but there is just one or two people
we would like to acknowledge specifically.
Government Appreciation Ceremony In Quito For Ecuador School Donated By Emmanuel TV
A particular welcome to General Carlos Medina of the Ecuadorian Army.
Along with him is Lieutenant Colonel Omar Cruz.
From the Ministry of Economic & Social Inclusion,
whom we worked very closely with in the distribution of aid,
we would like to particularly acknowledge the presence of Efren Reyes,
who is the Deputy Minister for Social Inclusion and an Assembly Member.
The Police Major, Byron Liger.
A particular welcome to Mrs Cinthia Glas, the wife of the Vice President of Ecuador.
Antonio Ordonez from the Ministry of Education.
He is here and we would like to acknowledge his presence.
We are very thankful and grateful to everyone in this room.
The names are too many to mention.
Let me mention one or two who worked very, very closely with us on this project in Ecuador.
Thanks of course to the Ministry of Education.
For the school building project, Architect John Glen Pisco and his team
worked phenomenally.
As I said, if I would thank everyone, we would not leave here tonight.
Thank you all so much for enabling us to have the joy of giving and sharing with you.
Now, we would like to invite General Carlos Medina
to come and say a few words.
Greetings to everyone here.
This gives me a great personal satisfaction.
General Carlos Medina
Director of Human Resources, Ecuador Military
On behalf of the military, I feel very honoured to be able to represent my institution
and my citizens to first of all welcome Prophet T.B. Joshua and his team to Ecuador.
We hope that he and the Emmanuel TV Team enjoy our country.
He wants to welcome you, T.B. Joshua, to this country and to thank you for everything.
It is not only a personal honour, it is a national satisfaction to express to Prophet T.B. Joshua
our heartfelt appreciation for all the aid that we have received.
Initially, they brought foodstuff and essential aid.
Today, they have built a school for our Ecuadorian children.
General Carlos Medina Appreciates T.B. Joshua For The School Donated By Emmanuel TV
It is a national satisfaction to be able to give thanks to T.B. Joshua,
who not only gave food and supplies, but also a complete school.
Once more, on behalf of the Ecuadorian Army, I would sincerely like to thank you for being
able to join you in this humanitarian work carried out by Prophet T.B. Joshua and Emmanuel TV.
I also feel very happy, being able, in the name of the Ecuadorian Army, to give support and help,
and again to thank Emmanuel TV and T.B. Joshua.
Finally, we invite you to enjoy the natural beauty of Ecuador
together with the beauty of the hearts of the Ecuadorian people.
May God bless all your work.
We are very honoured to have you in our country.
Thank you very much.
General Carlos Medina Appreciates T.B. Joshua For The School Donated By Emmanuel TV
We also would like to invite you to enjoy the beauties of our country - Ecuador,
and of course to have the possibility to know us from our heart; we have a lot of love.
General Carlos Medina Appreciates T.B. Joshua For The School Donated By Emmanuel TV
We also want to present you with some gifts.
General Carlos Medina Presents T.B. Joshua With A Symbol Of The Ecuadorian Army
Can you come closer?
With a lot of honour; and I'm very proud to show you...
This is from the army; the symbol of the army - Ecuadorian Army.
And the history of the Ecuadorian Army.
This is a souvenir - it is not to drink; it is only to be put on a shelf as a decoration.
It is the symbol of the middle of the world.
General Carlos Medina Appreciates T.B. Joshua For The School Donated By Emmanuel TV
T.B. JOSHUA OPENS SCHOOL IN ECUADOR 2017
The appreciation ceremony.
We need to acknowledge the presence of another important person here as well,
who is going to come forward now.
Eddy Sanchez from the city of Quito, a councillor of the city government here.
Ecuador Government Dignitaries Appreciate T.B. Joshua For The School Donated By Emmanuel TV
Please, come forward, sir.
Colonel Eddy Sanchez
Councillor of The Quito City Government Representing The Mayor Of Quito
The Word of God says, if you bless a prophet for being a prophet, you receive a prophet’s blessing.
If you bless the just for being the just, you receive the just’s blessing.
Colonel Eddy Sanchez
Councillor of The Quito City Government Representing The Mayor Of Quito
I come on behalf of the Mayor and Government Council of Quito to activate this Biblical principle:
to honour the prophet.
We want to give Prophet T.B. Joshua The Commendation Of Honour
for significant services to our city.
We want to give this recognition to T.B. Joshua for all the very important services to our city.
Ecuador Government Dignitaries Appreciate T.B. Joshua For The School Donated By Emmanuel TV
T.B. Joshua is Awarded Commendation Of Honour By Quito Government For Services To Ecuador
It is not only a gift;
this is a book given to you by the mayor,
not only to give you this honour...
When a prophet enters a place, he affects the territory, atmosphere and spiritual world.
We want you to affect all areas of our territory.
This is the start of a new time according to your calling to heal and deliver our land.
This Commendation of Honour is bestowed upon civilians, legal entities, citizens and foreigners
who have taken notable measures to rescue our communities.
And you, in April 2016, planted blessing and healing for our people.
T.B. Joshua is Awarded Commendation Of Honour By Quito Government For Services To Ecuador
Prophet, receive this honour as a Prophet and the city will be blessed by this honour.
We want to give you this gift, this book - it is about Quito; the land of orchids...
T.B. Joshua is Awarded Commendation Of Honour By Quito Government For Services To Ecuador
We are men of authority, members of the government council of the city of Quito.
We recognise authority in you.
We bless you and we thank you.
T.B. Joshua is Awarded Commendation Of Honour By Quito Government For Services To Humanity
Right now, we would like to invite Mr Antonio Ordonez, who is representing the Ministry of Education.
Mr Antonio Ordonez
Minister of Education Representative
I thank God for the opportunity to be present today.
Thank you, Prophet, for allowing God to use you to come to Ecuador when we needed you most.
True men of God are known in difficult circumstances.
On behalf of the Ministry of Education,
T.B. Joshua, we thank this globally recognised humanitarian organisation, Emmanuel TV.
Ecuador Ministry Of Education Presents T.B. Joshua With A Plaque Of Recognition
I want to read what the Ministry of Education, is presenting to Prophet T.B. Joshua,
because of what he has done here.
Ecuador Ministry Of Education Presents T.B. Joshua With A Plaque Of Recognition
The Minister for education, through direction number 1 wants to give an appreciation to Emmanuel TV.
This is an appreciation for what they have done in reconstructing and building of the school,
Juan Lorenzo Anapa in Chachi, in Esmeraldas province.
Carman Guagua, coordinator of the area, signed this appreciation; thank you.
The Ministry Of Education Recognises T.B. Joshua For His Services To Ecuador
T.B. JOSHUA OPENS SCHOOL IN ECUADOR 2017
The appreciations ceremony.
Pastor Modesto Montero, from the foundation for the outreach to the nations in Esmeraldas.
It is a great privilege for me tonight
and I am very exited.
I was in Mexico and God really amazed me by the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua.
The work that has taken place in Esmeraldas Province -
we were the foundation that had to put into practice what we had learned from him.
As a foundation we learned from him; we had an opportunity to apply it when the earthquake happened.
Publicly, I want to say that the Gospel that I preach changed.
We can’t preach the Word if we don’t meet the need of others.
I want to deeply appreciate Prophet T.B. Joshua for what he has done in our province.
My wife and I want to give you a hug this night.
Ecuador Government Dignitaries Appreciate T.B. Joshua For School Donated By Emmanuel TV
So, I’m at their service.
Thank you very much.
I just want to say thank you to you all.
Like the prophet has rightly said, we are at your service.
So, expect us very soon.
God bless you.
T.B. JOSHUA OPENS SCHOOL IN ECUADOR 2017
The appreciation ceremony.
We would just like to invite Cinthia Glas, the wife of the Vice President - let us welcome her.
Government Appreciation Ceremony In Quito For Ecuador School Donated By Emmanuel TV
Good evening.
The truth is that I am not used to speaking much in public.
But I know that God will give me the perfect words to appreciate this great man.
I appreciate him on behalf of my people and above all, God.
As the Word of God says in Psalm 41:1,
“Blessed is he that considers the poor: the Lord will deliver him in the time of trouble.”
I thank him so much on behalf of everyone.
You know how much we have suffered with the earthquake
but we also know the promise of the Lord that it will not happen again because God is merciful
and we are praying to Him – the true and living God.
Everybody knows how much we suffered because of the earthquake,
but we have the promise of God that something like that will not happen again.
The mercy and love of God are with us.
Also many thanks to all the people who joined the pastor in this great work
because without God’s help, nothing would have been possible.
We always know that we were never alone because we have a living God
and His name is the Lord of Hosts.
Government Appreciation Ceremony In Quito For Ecuador School Donated By Emmanuel TV
We also thank all those who joined the Emmanuel TV team to do this job,
because we know that without the help of God, we would not have been able to do it.
On behalf of my husband, my family and all the people of this nation, we thank you.
Government Appreciation Ceremony In Quito For Ecuador School Donated By Emmanuel TV
Cinthia Glas, Wife Of Vice President Of Ecuador Shows Appreciation To T.B. Joshua
So, finally, we would like to invite the representative of the Chachi community of San Salvador -
Mr Santiago to come and...
Emmanuel TV Team Welcomes The Representative Of The Chachi Community
Good evening, everyone.
This is a special moment not just for the guests present and the delegation from Emmanuel TV
but also for the community of San Salvador de Los Chachis for the monumental work
that we are inaugurating today.
This is a very special moment, not only for those who are here now - Emmanuel TV team,
but also for all of the Chachi community.
The videos and pictures show the process of the construction work and those who participated.
As you can see on the video and the pictures, they show the process of these amazing contributions.
The Chachi Community considers and appreciates what T.B. Joshua has done not only physically
but also spiritually and prophetically.
Mr Santiago, Chachi Community Representative Appreciates T.B. Joshua For New Ecuador School
The Chachi community appreciates what Prophet T.B. Joshua has done in our community;
not only a physical contribution and help - it has been a spiritual and prophetic help.
I say this because the school that collapsed in the earthquake was built 40 years ago.
This school was built by the hands of the community members.
This school is 40 years now and initially it was built by members of the community.
It was a blessing of God that something that we dreamt of a long time ago
has come to reality.
For us it is a great blessing from God, that what we always dreamt of, concerning the school,
has today materialized in our community.
The children – over 300 students and 14 teachers are very happy.
We as a community are also happy because our children don’t have to go through so much
difficulty in the education process as they had to before.
Now they have beautiful new classrooms to aid their learning.
More than 300 children from the school, the teachers and the whole community are very joyful
because now they can have their education in proper classrooms what they did not have before.
From the beginning of the construction process, the community joyfully received
the presence of Emmanuel TV and we had the faith and assurance that the job would be
carried out with success in line with the vision of the project.
From the beginning, we were very happy to receive the Emmanuel TV team,
and we truly believed that this work would be fulfilled.
We were sure that God was with us and with the power that God gave T.B. Joshua,
this project would be completed.
Mr Santiago, Chachi Community Representative Appreciates T.B. Joshua For New Ecuador School
We were sure that God was with us, and the power that God has given to Prophet T.B. Joshua
would make this dream come real in our community.
On behalf of my community and the Chachi people of Ecuador, I want to convey
this joy and appreciation to T.B. Joshua, the Emmanuel TV team and everyone
who worked with the foundation as well as the technical team under the architect
and all those who came together to make this dream come true.
On behalf of the Chachi community of Ecuador, we appreciate Prophet T.B. Joshua for what he has done,
and we also appreciate all those who joined in this amazing job.
The Juan Lorenzo Anapa School Built & Donated By Emmanuel TV
On behalf of the community, we also want to express our desire for T.B. Joshua
with the help of God to continue aiding the needy all over the world
in disaster-affected areas like ours.
As a community we want to tell T.B. Joshua, with the help of God, to continue helping the needy,
when they face this kind of natural disasters.
We know that in humanitarian work, distance is not a barrier.
Nigeria is a faraway country compared to Ecuador
but the humanitarian aid reached us and today we have Prophet T.B. Joshua in our midst
in Ecuador for which we feel very blessed.
Government Appreciation Ceremony In Quito For Ecuador School Donated By Emmanuel TV
We learned that when someone wants to help, there is no barrier, there is no distance,
because you are coming all the way from Nigeria which is very far to come and help us.
We really appreciate that.
Government Appreciation Ceremony In Quito For Ecuador School Donated By Emmanuel TV
We are immensely grateful to Emmanuel TV and Prophet T.B. Joshua for
the magnificent school built in our community.
Thank you and God bless you.
Government Appreciation Ceremony In Quito For Ecuador School Donated By Emmanuel TV
Thank you very much.
T.B. JOSHUA OPENS SCHOOL IN ECUADOR 2017
The appreciation ceremony.
The Rabbi would like to come and say a few words.
Rabbi Yehuda Meshi Zahav
Founder, ZAKA – Israeli Search And Rescue
Good evening, everybody.
It took us 26 hours of flying to get here for such a special occasion this evening.
ZAKA’s Rabbi Yehuda Appreciates T.B. Joshua And Greets Ecuadorian Dignitaries
My organisation, ZAKA, has unfortunately seen a lot of disasters in the last few decades.
ZAKA’s Founder Rabbi Yehuda Addresses Dignitaries At The Appreciation Ceremony
It is so wonderful to go and do things together with Prophet T.B. Joshua in his unique organisation.
Government Appreciation Ceremony In Quito For Ecuador School Donated By Emmanuel TV
It is a privilege and honour that ZAKA and Emmanuel TV – two big organisations -
gather together to help others around the world.
ZAKA’s Founder Rabbi Yehuda Addresses Dignitaries At The Appreciation Ceremony
The Bible says that God created people; it doesn’t say what colour or what nation they were from.
He created people and we are supposed to help each and every person
wherever they are and whatever they believe.
ZAKA’s Founder Rabbi Yehuda Addresses Dignitaries At The Appreciation Ceremony
We are all brothers and are here to help each other in good times and in disasters.
So, when someone from our family is in trouble, we are here to help in whatever way we can.
ZAKA’s Founder Rabbi Yehuda Addresses Dignitaries At The Appreciation Ceremony
Government Appreciation Ceremony In Quito For Ecuador School Donated By Emmanuel TV
God wants us to work together and help each other by sharing our knowledge and love.
ZAKA’s Founder Rabbi Yehuda Addresses Dignitaries At The Appreciation Ceremony
The Bible says that if you save one life, it is like you have saved the whole world.
To save lives is not just by giving someone CPR or helping if they have a fracture.
ZAKA’s Founder Rabbi Yehuda Addresses Dignitaries At The Appreciation Ceremony
For the prophet to build a school for the students, they will learn more and teach their children
and it becomes a project for life.
ZAKA’s Founder Rabbi Yehuda Addresses Dignitaries At The Appreciation Ceremony
Like the prophet said in the meeting with the Vice President, ZAKA is here
to help you train people so that if this happens again, you can save more lives.
ZAKA’s Founder Rabbi Yehuda Addresses Dignitaries At The Appreciation Ceremony
Government Appreciation Ceremony In Quito For Ecuador School Donated By Emmanuel TV
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
ZAKA’s Founder Rabbi Yehuda Addresses Dignitaries At The Appreciation Ceremony
So, thank you very much, Rabbi Meshi Zahav, founder of ZAKA.
And now as we bring the proceedings to a close,
could we invite the Chachi community to come forward please.
Members Of The Chachi Community Perform A Traditional Dance
Emmanuel TV Team Give Out Ministry Materials To Ecuadorian Dignitaries & Guests
With the event drawn to a successful conclusion, the Emmanuel TV team hands out gift packages
to the dignitaries and guests, containing books by T.B. Joshua and materials
highlighting Emmanuel TV's charitable activities around the world.
The event is over and the distinguished guests and attendees begin to take their leave.
T.B. JOSHUA OPENS SCHOOL IN ECUADOR 2017
The opening of the school.
Let us go back to the last words of T.B. Joshua on the opening day of the school donated by Emmanuel TV.
We give all glory to God!
I was with the Vice President yesterday.
I am going to have another meeting to let him know what I went through to come here today.
We cannot allow our children to continue like this.
It is too tense for our children.
They have to find something to do – most especially on the roads to this place.
Thank you very much.
ECUADOR CHARITY OUTTAKERS
TB JOSHUA IN THE TROPICAL RAINFOREST
I’M RUNNING OUT OF FOOD!
WE’VE RUN OUT OF FOOD!
THE CAR IS STUCK IN THE MUD!
A HORSE COMES TO THE RESCUE!
DON’T WORRY, A RIDE IS COMING!
IF YOU CAN GET ON THE HORSE!
1, 2, 3, UP!
IT'S NOT EASY TO DO CHARITY!
WHERE ARE MY SHOES?
RAW CHARITY: T.B. Joshua As You Have NEVER Seen Him!!!
WATCH THE CAMERAMAN SLIDING THROUGH THE MUD!
EMMANUEL
GOD WITH US!
TT ROBERT BEGIER 25/10/2018
RV: Mel Flowers 01/11/2018